[Speed and Love]
[السرعة والحب]
[Episode 24]
[الحلقة 24]
Here.
هنا.
Take a seat. I'll go take a shower.
تفضل بالجلوس. سأذهب لأستحم.
You're showering in his place?
هل تستحمين في مكانه؟
I stay here.
سأبقى هنا.
You...
أنت...
I can't stand it. I smell terrible.
لا أطيق ذلك. رائحتي كريهة.
It's unbearable.
إنه أمر لا يُطاق.
A bunch of men were smoking around me tonight.
كان هناك مجموعة من الرجال يدخنون حولي الليلة.
I can't stand the smell of smoke.
لا أطيق رائحة الدخان.
Make yourself at home.
البيت بيتك.
You got a phone call just now.
لقد تلقيت مكالمة هاتفية الآن.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
It was from a little boy.
كانت من صبي صغير.
It must be my son.
لا بد أنه ابني.
Son?
ابن؟
Jin Zhao's?
جين تشاو؟
What?
ماذا؟
Is Jin Zhao your son's father?
هل جين تشاو هو والد ابنك؟
What are you talking about?
عن ماذا تتحدث؟
My son has already graduated from college.
لقد تخرج ابني بالفعل من الجامعة.
College?
كلية؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I accidentally saw your phone wallpaper.
رأيتُ خلفية هاتفك بالصدفة.
A 5 or 6-year-old boy was calling you.
كان يتصل بك صبي يبلغ من العمر 5 أو 6 سنوات.
The wallpaper is my younger son.
ورق الحائط هو صورة ابني الأصغر.
He's about 5 or 6 years old.
عمره حوالي 5 أو 6 سنوات.
So...
لذا...
Your younger son's father...
والد ابنك الأصغر...
Is he...
هل هو...
Not Jin Zhao.
ليس جين تشاو.
Young lady, what are you thinking?
يا آنسة، ما الذي تفكرين فيه؟
Do you know how old I am?
هل تعلم كم عمري؟
32?
32؟
I'm almost 50.
أنا على مشارف الخمسين.
If I tried hard enough,
لو بذلت جهدًا كافيًا،
I could have another child your age.
بإمكاني إنجاب طفل آخر في عمرك.
How could I possibly have something to do with Jin Zhao?
كيف يمكن أن يكون لي علاقة بجين تشاو؟
You look amazing for your age.
تبدو رائعاً بالنسبة لعمرك.
I thought...
ظننت...
I thought you...
ظننتك...
Thought I was Jin Zhao's wife?
ظننت أنني زوجة جين تشاو؟
Your name is...
اسمك هو...
Mu?
في؟
No wonder.
لا عجب في ذلك.
You looked familiar when I saw you at the door.
بدا وجهك مألوفاً عندما رأيتك عند الباب.
It just didn't come to mind immediately.
لم يخطر ببالي الأمر على الفور.
Come with me.
تعال معي.
This is Jin Zhao's rehabilitation room. Please come in.
هذه غرفة إعادة تأهيل جين تشاو. تفضل بالدخول.
Is that little girl in the photo you?
هل تلك الفتاة الصغيرة في الصورة أنتِ؟
Let me properly introduce myself.
دعوني أقدم نفسي بشكل لائق.
I'm Jin Zhao's personal physician, Julia.
أنا الطبيبة الشخصية لجين تشاو، جوليا.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Personal...
شخصي...
During the first two years after Jin Zhao's accident,
خلال السنتين الأوليين بعد حادث جين تشاو،
his condition was terrible.
كانت حالته مروعة.
He often experienced pain throughout his body.
كان يشعر بالألم في جميع أنحاء جسده في كثير من الأحيان.
During the worst episodes,
خلال أسوأ الحلقات،
I had to give him sedatives.
اضطررت لإعطائه مهدئات.
When he wasn't fully conscious,
عندما لم يكن واعياً تماماً،
he kept mumbling,
ظل يتمتم،
"Mu...
"في...
Mu..."
في..."
I didn't understand at the time.
لم أفهم ذلك في ذلك الوقت.
I thought it was
ظننت ذلك
the English word "Moon."
الكلمة الإنجليزية "Moon".
Later someone told me
أخبرني أحدهم لاحقاً
that actually
هذا في الواقع
it was a girl's name:
كان اسم فتاة:
Jiang Mu.
جيانغ مو.
Your name is Jiang Mu?
اسمك جيانغ مو؟
What has he
ماذا لديه
been through all these years?
هل مرّت كل هذه السنوات؟
I was also hired by someone.
لقد تم توظيفي أيضاً من قبل شخص ما.
Lin Sui brought me back from Canada
أعادني لين سوي من كندا
to take charge of Jin Zhao's rehabilitation.
لتولي مسؤولية إعادة تأهيل جين تشاو.
I stayed with him in Chaguo for a year,
مكثت معه في تشاغوو لمدة عام.
which was also when he was in his worst condition.
وكان ذلك أيضاً عندما كان في أسوأ حالاته.
You could say
يمكنك أن تقول
he was on the brink of death.
كان على حافة الموت.
Later,
لاحقاً،
when his condition improved a bit,
عندما تحسنت حالته قليلاً،
he insisted on returning to China, to Nanjing.
أصرّ على العودة إلى الصين، إلى نانجينغ.
Lin Sui and I both disagreed.
لم نتفق أنا ولين سوي على ذلك.
Lin Sui talked to him many times.
تحدث لين سوي معه مرات عديدة.
But he was very determined.
لكنه كان مصمماً للغاية.
So we discussed it,
لذا ناقشنا الأمر،
and I decided to return to China with him
وقررت العودة إلى الصين معه
to live with him
أن يعيش معه
and take care of him.
واعتني به.
I'm staying in the guest room.
سأقيم في غرفة الضيوف.
At that time,
في ذلك الوقت،
his condition was very unstable.
كانت حالته غير مستقرة للغاية.
I was on call day and night.
كنتُ على أهبة الاستعداد ليلاً ونهاراً.
If he hadn't worn me out,
لو لم يكن قد أرهقني،
I'd probably look much younger,
ربما سأبدو أصغر سناً بكثير،
maybe
ربما
about 28 years old.
يبلغ من العمر حوالي 28 عامًا.
[Jin Zhao]
[جين تشاو]
It's Jin Zhao.
إنه جين تشاو.
Jin Zhao.
جين تشاو.
I've brought back all the medicine you need,
لقد أحضرت كل الأدوية التي تحتاجها،
and wrote down all the instructions.
ودوّن جميع التعليمات.
I'm not going back to Canada.
لن أعود إلى كندا.
Of course,
بالطبع،
if you don't need me around
إذا لم تكن بحاجة لوجودي.
and have someone else to keep you company,
وأن يكون لديك شخص آخر ليؤنسك،
I wouldn't mind taking some time off.
لا مانع لدي من أخذ إجازة لبعض الوقت.
My eldest
ابني الأكبر
has been asking me to go to his graduation ceremony for ages.
يطلب مني منذ مدة طويلة أن أحضر حفل تخرجه.
I want to go.
أريد أن أذهب.
I don't believe you can
لا أعتقد أنك تستطيع
take care of yourself.
اعتنِ بنفسك.
Fine.
بخير.
Without this old witch—me—around,
بدون وجود هذه العجوز الساحرة - أنا - حولي،
go find your little angel.
اذهب وابحث عن ملاكك الصغير.
Fine. Bye.
حسناً. مع السلامة.
Jin Zhao has had
جين تشاو لديه
a very difficult time these years.
لقد كانت هذه السنوات فترة صعبة للغاية.
It's really good that you can be
من الجيد حقاً أن تكون
back by his side again.
عادت إلى جانبه مرة أخرى.
Jin Zhao is truly strong.
جين تشاو قوي حقاً.
He has extraordinary willpower.
لديه إرادة قوية بشكل استثنائي.
You must not give up on him.
لا يجب أن تتخلى عنه.
[Purple Mountain Observatory]
[مرصد الجبل الأرجواني]
Nana.
نانا.
This is from Director Wang.
هذا من المخرج وانغ.
It's for Monday's meeting.
هذا لاجتماع يوم الاثنين.
Okay.
تمام.
Mu.
في.
This is our schedule.
هذا هو جدولنا الزمني.
On Monday, we need to confirm
يوم الاثنين، نحتاج إلى التأكيد
the venue setup.
تجهيز المكان.
You might need to double-check everything.
قد تحتاج إلى إعادة التحقق من كل شيء.
Okay.
تمام.
That's about it.
هذا كل ما في الأمر.
You...
أنت...
Hello, to Manshi please.
مرحباً، إلى مانشي من فضلك.
Alright, please wait a moment.
حسنًا، انتظر لحظة من فضلك.
Do you have any luggage to check in?
هل لديك أي أمتعة لتسجيلها؟
The boarding gate is this way.
بوابة الصعود إلى الطائرة من هذا الاتجاه.
-Have a good trip. -Thank you.
أتمنى لك رحلة سعيدة. - شكراً لك.
You're Jiang Mu, right?
أنت جيانغ مو، أليس كذلك؟
Dr. Julia asked me
سألتني الدكتورة جوليا
to give you this medical file.
لأعطيك هذا الملف الطبي.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Jiang Mu.
جيانغ مو.
I know you're in Chaguo now.
أعلم أنك في تشاغوو الآن.
Why wasn't I told anything?
لماذا لم يتم إخباري بأي شيء؟
Since you know everything now,
بما أنك تعرف كل شيء الآن،
what do you plan to do?
ما الذي تنوي فعله؟
[Patient Medical Report]
[تقرير طبي للمريض]
Is there any news
هل من أخبار؟
from Jin Zhao?
من جين تشاو؟
He hasn't been back physically.
لم يعد جسديًا.
We haven't heard much from him in a long time.
لم نسمع عنه الكثير منذ فترة طويلة.
Yeah, it's been so many years since he returned.
نعم، لقد مرت سنوات عديدة منذ عودته.
Who knows,
من يدري،
maybe he's already settled down somewhere else.
ربما يكون قد استقر بالفعل في مكان آخر.
I might have some bad news for you.
قد يكون لدي بعض الأخبار السيئة لك.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Lightning is missing.
البرق مفقود.
Missing?
مفتقد؟
Then I got a call from a stranger.
ثم تلقيت مكالمة من شخص غريب.
He said he had the goods
قال إنه يملك البضائع
and quoted me a price.
وأعطاني سعراً.
I thought it was a scam,
ظننت أنها عملية احتيال.
so I insisted on meeting in person.
لذلك أصررتُ على اللقاء شخصياً.
To my surprise,
لدهشتي،
it was Brandy!
كانت براندي!
You're still young.
ما زلت صغيراً.
We'll have plenty of time in the future.
سيكون لدينا متسع من الوقت في المستقبل.
But your mom can't wait.
لكن والدتك لا تستطيع الانتظار.
After major surgery,
بعد إجراء عملية جراحية كبرى،
a patient's mood is the most important thing.
إن الحالة المزاجية للمريض هي أهم شيء.
If you stay with her,
إذا بقيت معها،
she will feel better.
ستشعر بتحسن.
It's good for her recovery.
إنه مفيد لشفائها.
[Jin Zhao]
[جين تشاو]
Are you busy?
هل أنت مشغول؟
I'm at home.
أنا في المنزل.
Do you have time to meet up?
هل لديك وقت للقاء؟
I have something for you.
لدي شيء لك.
No.
لا.
Then when will you have time?
إذن متى سيكون لديك الوقت؟
Come for a walk with me this weekend.
تعالوا في نزهة معي في نهاية هذا الأسبوع.
Forget it if you don't want to.
انسَ الأمر إن لم ترغب بذلك.
Anyway, back then
على أي حال، في ذلك الوقت
you promised to take me out but never did.
لقد وعدتني بالخروج معي لكنك لم تفعل ذلك أبداً.
I still remember that.
ما زلت أتذكر ذلك.
Will going for a walk make you less angry?
هل سيجعلك المشي أقل غضباً؟
No.
لا.
So are you still going?
هل ما زلت ستذهب؟
Yes.
نعم.
Let's go for a walk this weekend.
لنذهب في نزهة هذا الأسبوع.
Why are you just standing there?
لماذا تقف هناك فقط؟
I'm looking at how you haven't changed at all.
ألاحظ كيف أنك لم تتغير على الإطلاق.
What about me?
ماذا عني؟
♪ What was it that brought me to you? ♪
♪ ما الذي أوصلني إليك؟ ♪
Have I changed a lot?
هل تغيرت كثيراً؟
♪ Perhaps it was fate's design ♪
♪ ربما كان ذلك من تدبير القدر ♪
♪ Through all our winding paths, we always find each other ♪
♪ عبر جميع مساراتنا المتعرجة، نجد بعضنا البعض دائمًا ♪
Quite a lot.
كثير جدًا.
♪ The storm turned to rain, and everything was swept away ♪
♪ تحولت العاصفة إلى مطر، وجرف كل شيء ♪
Was I prettier before or now?
هل كنت أجمل من قبل أم الآن؟
♪ Slowly, everything becomes clear ♪
♪ شيئًا فشيئًا، يتضح كل شيء ♪
♪ In your gaze ♪
♪ في نظرتك ♪
I only want a three-word answer.
أريد إجابة من ثلاث كلمات فقط.
♪ I found the answer ♪
♪ لقد وجدتُ الإجابة ♪
♪ There's a feeling so strong ♪
♪ هناك شعور قوي للغاية ♪
You're always beautiful.
أنتِ جميلة دائماً.
♪ Our story is still unfolding ♪
♪ قصتنا لا تزال تتكشف ♪
♪ Waiting for the perfect ending ♪
♪ في انتظار النهاية المثالية ♪
♪ It all began the moment I met you ♪
♪ بدأ كل شيء في اللحظة التي التقيت بك فيها ♪
♪ There's a pull I cannot explain ♪
♪ هناك جاذبية لا أستطيع تفسيرها ♪
♪ My eyes follow you, my heart chases after you ♪
♪ عيناي تتبعانك، وقلبي يلاحقك ♪
Brother,
أخ،
when will we get there? I'm so tired.
متى سنصل إلى هناك؟ أنا متعب جداً.
♪ I just can't help it ♪
♪ لا أستطيع منع نفسي ♪
♪ When I gaze across the sky ♪
♪ عندما أنظر عبر السماء ♪
We're almost there.
لقد اقتربنا من الوصول.
Just a few more steps and we'll see the sunset.
بضع خطوات أخرى فقط وسنرى غروب الشمس.
♪ Not even miles can keep us apart ♪
♪ حتى الأميال لا تستطيع أن تفرق بيننا ♪
But Brother, I really can't walk anymore.
لكن يا أخي، لم أعد أستطيع المشي حقاً.
♪ Sweet longing drifts on the wind ♪
♪ شوقٌ عذبٌ ينجرف مع الريح ♪
I'm stopping here.
سأتوقف هنا.
I'll just sit right here.
سأجلس هنا فقط.
♪ I can feel you near ♪
♪ أشعر بوجودك بالقرب مني ♪
Come on.
تعال.
♪ Feel you're with me ♪
♪ أشعر أنك معي ♪
Don't worry, I'm here.
لا تقلق، أنا هنا.
I'll help you walk up.
سأساعدك في الصعود.
♪ Forget the sunsets, forget the tides ♪
♪ انسَ غروب الشمس، انسَ المد والجزر ♪
♪ Watch the years pass and wander the world ♪
♪ شاهد مرور السنين وتجول في العالم ♪
♪ You're the only one in my heart ♪
♪ أنتِ الوحيدة في قلبي ♪
♪ It all began the moment I met you ♪
♪ بدأ كل شيء في اللحظة التي التقيت بك فيها ♪
♪ The road ahead ♪
♪ الطريق أمامنا ♪
♪ And every step we take ♪
♪ وكل خطوة نخطوها ♪
♪ Guide us toward happiness ♪
♪ أرشدنا نحو السعادة ♪
Here we are.
ها نحن ذا.
♪ Just to see you ♪
♪ فقط لأراك ♪
Here you go.
ها أنت ذا.
Why are you giving me a phone?
لماذا تعطيني هاتفاً؟
Didn't you say you wanted to replace your phone after using it for years?
ألم تقل إنك تريد استبدال هاتفك بعد استخدامه لسنوات؟
Since you're often out,
بما أنك غالباً ما تكون خارج المنزل،
you should use something better.
يجب عليك استخدام شيء أفضل.
Is that funny?
هل هذا مضحك؟
Will you believe anything I say?
هل ستصدق أي شيء أقوله؟
Being like this,
أن تكون على هذا النحو،
you'll easily get scammed by other girls.
ستتعرض بسهولة للاحتيال من قبل فتيات أخريات.
You're not "other girls."
أنتِ لستِ "فتيات أخريات".
Then what am I?
إذن ما أنا؟
Um,
واحد،
before we start, I need to confirm something.
قبل أن نبدأ، أحتاج إلى تأكيد شيء ما.
You're still single, right?
ما زلت عازباً، أليس كذلك؟
What does being single have to do with this?
ما علاقة كون الشخص أعزب بهذا؟
Of course it does.
بالطبع يفعل ذلك.
I'm a person with principles.
أنا شخص ذو مبادئ.
I would never interfere in someone else's relationship.
لن أتدخل أبداً في علاقة شخص آخر.
So I must confirm.
لذا يجب عليّ التأكيد.
I thought we were just going for a walk?
ظننت أننا سنذهب في نزهة فقط؟
What?
ماذا؟
What are you planning to do to me here
ما الذي تنوي فعله بي هنا؟
that involves interfering in relationships?
وهذا ينطوي على التدخل في العلاقات؟
You don't seem to have any concerns.
لا يبدو أن لديك أي مخاوف.
Aren't you worried that my boyfriend might mind
ألا تخشى أن يمانع صديقي؟
that you got me a new phone?
هل اشتريت لي هاتفًا جديدًا؟
If he minds, can't he buy one himself?
إذا كان يمانع، ألا يستطيع شراء واحدة بنفسه؟
His money
ماله
is for buying gaming equipment.
يُستخدم لشراء معدات الألعاب.
Why did you walk off by yourself?
لماذا ذهبت وحدك؟
Have you climbed this mountain before?
هل سبق لك أن تسلقت هذا الجبل؟
No.
لا.
Isn't the coffee shop very close to here?
أليس المقهى قريباً جداً من هنا؟
Why didn't you come climbing?
لماذا لم تأتِ للتسلق؟
No reason.
لا يوجد سبب.
When did you start liking photography?
متى بدأت تحب التصوير؟
What are you photographing?
ما الذي تقوم بتصويره؟
Try feeling it.
حاول أن تشعر به.
I don't quite feel it.
لا أشعر بذلك تماماً.
Capturing nature's soul.
التقاط روح الطبيعة.
How did I never notice before
كيف لم ألاحظ ذلك من قبل؟
that you're so good at talking nonsense?
أنك بارعٌ جداً في قول الهراء؟
I noticed it at the coffee shop.
لاحظت ذلك في المقهى.
Why do you keep wearing it?
لماذا تستمر في ارتدائه؟
Let's compete.
هيا نتنافس.
Let's see who's faster.
لنرى من الأسرع.
No.
لا.
Why not?
ولم لا؟
You go first.
ابدأ أنت أولاً.
I'll catch up with you.
سألحق بك.
I'll wait for you up there.
سأنتظرك هناك في الأعلى.
This is far enough.
هذا يكفي.
He should be able to keep up, right?
ينبغي أن يكون قادراً على مواكبة ذلك، أليس كذلك؟
Zhao.
تشاو.
Why don't you tell me
لماذا لا تخبرني أنت؟
about your health condition?
ماذا عن حالتك الصحية؟
Jin Zhao!
جين تشاو!
Are you going to hide forever?
هل ستختبئ إلى الأبد؟
That day I went to your place,
في ذلك اليوم ذهبت إلى منزلك،
Dr. Julia told me everything.
أخبرتني الدكتورة جوليا بكل شيء.
I also went to Manshi.
ذهبتُ أيضاً إلى مانشي.
I saw all your medical reports.
لقد اطلعت على جميع تقاريرك الطبية.
Why didn't you tell me?
لماذا لم تخبرني؟
If I hadn't gone to your house,
لو لم أذهب إلى منزلك،
how long were you going to hide it from me?
إلى متى كنت ستخفيه عني؟
For the rest of your life?
لبقية حياتك؟
♪ Forgotten between the rearview mirror ♪
♪ منسي بين مرآة الرؤية الخلفية ♪
♪ Seeing your long unseen face on that rainy night ♪
♪ رؤية وجهك الذي لم أره منذ زمن طويل في تلك الليلة الماطرة ♪
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I was thinking
كنت أفكر
♪ Counting backwards to the unfulfilled promises ♪
♪ العد التنازلي للوعود التي لم تتحقق ♪
I would go look for you
سأذهب للبحث عنك
when my condition improved.
عندما تحسنت حالتي.
♪ The heart that is still beating hasn't said goodbye yet ♪
♪ القلب الذي لا يزال ينبض لم يودع بعد ♪
Why?
لماذا؟
♪ Meeting again after many years ♪
♪ لقاء جديد بعد سنوات عديدة ♪
Why did all of you keep this from me?
لماذا أخفيتم هذا الأمر عني جميعاً؟
♪ The coffee is too sour and bitter; I'm greedy for something sweet ♪
♪ القهوة حامضة ومرة ​​للغاية؛ أنا أتوق إلى شيء حلو ♪
Why didn't you tell me?
لماذا لم تخبرني؟
♪ Who will circle around the line bordering the thoughts? ♪
♪ من سيحيط بالخط الفاصل بين الأفكار؟ ♪
No matter what，
مهما حدث،
♪ Stupidly, I refuse to believe there's an end ♪
♪ بغباء، أرفض تصديق أن هناك نهاية ♪
you should have at least let me know.
كان ينبغي عليك على الأقل إخباري.
♪ I must ♪
♪ يجب عليّ ♪
♪ Continue to love, between the sun and the moon ♪
♪ استمر في الحب، بين الشمس والقمر ♪
♪ Even in pain, we indulge in the iron-like vows ♪
♪ حتى في الألم، نتمسك بالعهود الحديدية ♪
(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
(شاهد على www.dramacool.club دعم الإدارة)
♪ Willingly ♪
♪ عن طيب خاطر ♪
♪ At this moment ♪
♪ في هذه اللحظة ♪
You were still young then.
كنت لا تزال صغيراً حينها.
I couldn't bear to.
لم أستطع تحمل ذلك.
♪ I run towards you before the night falls ♪
♪ أركض نحوك قبل حلول الليل ♪
But you could bear not contacting me at all?
لكن هل يمكنك تحمل عدم الاتصال بي على الإطلاق؟
♪ Don't ask about the past; just bet on tomorrow ♪
♪ لا تسأل عن الماضي؛ راهن فقط على الغد ♪
♪ Those dreams and longings ♪
♪ تلك الأحلام والتطلعات ♪
Jin Zhao...
جين تشاو ...
You're so heartless.
أنت عديم الرحمة للغاية.
♪ I really want to fill the void of regret ♪
♪ أريد حقاً أن أملأ فراغ الندم ♪
♪ My longing has left the bow ♪
♪ لقد فارقت رغبتي القوس ♪
♪ Shooting out into the horizon ♪
♪ إطلاق النار نحو الأفق ♪
♪ Meeting again after many years ♪
♪ لقاء جديد بعد سنوات عديدة ♪
♪ The coffee is too sour; I'm greedy for something sweet ♪
♪ القهوة حامضة جداً؛ أنا أتوق إلى شيء حلو ♪
At first,
في البداية،
♪ Who will circle around the line bordering the thoughts? ♪
♪ من سيحيط بالخط الفاصل بين الأفكار؟ ♪
♪ Stupidly, I refuse to believe there's an end ♪
♪ بغباء، أرفض تصديق أن هناك نهاية ♪
my condition wasn't good.
لم تكن حالتي جيدة.
♪ I must ♪
♪ يجب عليّ ♪
I didn't know if I could make it.
لم أكن أعرف ما إذا كنت سأتمكن من فعل ذلك.
♪ Continue to love, between the sun and the moon ♪
♪ استمر في الحب، بين الشمس والقمر ♪
So I made Sanlai promise me
لذلك جعلت سانلاي يعدني بذلك
♪ Even in pain, we indulge in the iron-like vows ♪
♪ حتى في الألم، نتمسك بالعهود الحديدية ♪
not to tell you the truth.
ليس لأقول لك الحقيقة.
♪ Willingly ♪
♪ عن طيب خاطر ♪
Later I pulled through,
ثم تعافيت،
but I didn't even have a place to stay.
لكن لم يكن لديّ حتى مكان أقيم فيه.
♪ At this moment ♪
♪ في هذه اللحظة ♪
In that situation,
في تلك الحالة،
♪ I run towards you before the night falls ♪
♪ أركض نحوك قبل حلول الليل ♪
I couldn't contact you.
لم أتمكن من الاتصال بك.
♪ Don't ask about the past; just bet on tomorrow ♪
♪ لا تسأل عن الماضي؛ راهن فقط على الغد ♪
Then why
فلماذا
did you suddenly appear in my life again now?
هل ظهرت فجأة في حياتي مرة أخرى الآن؟
♪ Those dreams and longings ♪
♪ تلك الأحلام والتطلعات ♪
♪ Look at the days that have passed ♪
♪ انظر إلى الأيام التي مضت ♪
♪ Those were yesterday's youth ♪
♪ هؤلاء كانوا شباب الأمس ♪
♪ Look at the people parting in the crowd ♪
♪ انظر إلى الناس وهم يتفرقون في الحشد ♪
♪ They used to love each other the most ♪
♪ كانا يحبان بعضهما البعض أكثر من أي شيء آخر ♪
♪ Look at what the vast world wants ♪
♪ انظروا ماذا يريد العالم الواسع ♪
Are you...
أنت...
♪ It's nothing but a fairytale ♪
♪ إنها مجرد حكاية خيالية ♪
Are you trying to reconcile with me?
هل تحاولين التصالح معي؟
♪ It's always the broken up couple ♪
♪ دائمًا ما يكون الأمر متعلقًا بالزوجين المنفصلين ♪
♪ Who reunite amidst love, hate, and separation ♪
♪ الذين يجتمعون من جديد وسط الحب والكراهية والفراق ♪
♪ I must ♪
♪ يجب عليّ ♪
♪ Continue to love, between the sun and the moon ♪
♪ استمر في الحب، بين الشمس والقمر ♪
♪ Even in pain, we indulge in the iron-like vows ♪
♪ حتى في الألم، نتمسك بالعهود الحديدية ♪
♪ Willingly ♪
♪ عن طيب خاطر ♪
♪ At this moment ♪
♪ في هذه اللحظة ♪
♪ I run towards you before the night falls ♪
♪ أركض نحوك قبل حلول الليل ♪
♪ Don't ask about the past ♪
♪ لا تسأل عن الماضي ♪
♪ Just bet on tomorrow ♪
♪ راهن على الغد ♪
♪ Those dreams and longings ♪
♪ تلك الأحلام والتطلعات ♪
♪ The trails overlap again ♪
♪ تتداخل المسارات مرة أخرى ♪
Later,
لاحقاً،
when his condition improved slightly,
عندما تحسنت حالته قليلاً،
he insisted on returning to China, to Nanjing.
أصرّ على العودة إلى الصين، إلى نانجينغ.
Lin Sui and I both disagreed.
لم نتفق أنا ولين سوي على ذلك.
Lin Sui spent a long time
أمضى لين سوي وقتاً طويلاً
trying to talk him out of it.
محاولة إقناعه بالعدول عن ذلك.
But he was very determined.
لكنه كان مصمماً للغاية.
Why did he insist on coming back to China?
لماذا أصرّ على العودة إلى الصين؟
Why did he buy the old house?
لماذا اشترى المنزل القديم؟
You want to meet Jiang Mu? Are you crazy or am I crazy?
أتريد مقابلة جيانغ مو؟ هل أنت مجنون أم أنا المجنون؟
Her mom is sick.
والدتها مريضة.
She needs to go to Canada.
إنها بحاجة للذهاب إلى كندا.
I must let her know I'm okay
يجب أن أطمئنها بأنني بخير
so she can stay in Canada with peace of mind
حتى تتمكن من البقاء في كندا براحة بال
and accompany her mother for medical treatment.
وترافق والدتها لتلقي العلاج الطبي.
Brandy,
براندي،
tell me how you're going to meet her.
أخبرني كيف ستلتقي بها.
Like this?
مثله؟
How?
كيف؟
Look at your condition.
انظر إلى حالتك.
You'll scare Jiang Mu to death.
ستخيف جيانغ مو حتى الموت.
Besides, the doctors would never allow it.
فضلاً عن ذلك، لن يسمح الأطباء بذلك أبداً.
Don't worry about the doctors.
لا تقلق بشأن الأطباء.
Officer Lu will help us with that.
سيساعدنا الضابط لو في ذلك.
What I need you to do now
ما أريدك أن تفعله الآن
is take me to the coffee shop
هل تأخذني إلى المقهى؟
and then bring Mu over.
ثم أحضر مو.
Brandy,
براندي،
let's think this through.
دعونا نفكر في هذا الأمر ملياً.
You barely survived.
لقد نجوت بأعجوبة.
What if something goes wrong again?
ماذا لو حدث خطأ ما مرة أخرى؟
Sanlai,
سانلاي،
I've made up my mind.
لقد حسمت أمري.
Brandy!
براندي!
Are you okay? Get up.
هل أنت بخير؟ انهض.
Come on.
تعال.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
I'll take you to the hospital.
سآخذك إلى المستشفى.
Looking at her tear-reddened eyes,
بالنظر إلى عينيها المحمرتين من الدموع،
I wanted so badly to hold her,
كنت أرغب بشدة في احتضانها،
but I couldn't.
لكنني لم أستطع.
I only want her to be happy,
كل ما أريده هو أن تكون سعيدة،
even if that happiness
حتى لو كانت تلك السعادة
doesn't include me.
لا يشملني ذلك.
[Jin Zhao]
[جين تشاو]
Jin Zhao's rehabilitation is very tough.
إعادة تأهيل جين تشاو صعبة للغاية.
You need to encourage him more.
عليك تشجيعه أكثر.
Observe his physical reactions.
راقب ردود فعله الجسدية.
Pay attention to Jin Zhao's
انتبه إلى جين تشاو
complexion and breathing for any abnormalities.
فحص البشرة والتنفس بحثاً عن أي تشوهات.
If dizziness or severe pain occurs,
في حالة حدوث دوار أو ألم شديد،
stop immediately and contact me.
توقف فوراً واتصل بي.
[Purple Mountain Observatory]
[مرصد الجبل الأرجواني]
Mu, I'm leaving now.
مو، سأغادر الآن.
See you tomorrow.
أراك غداً.
Nana.
نانا.
It's Mid-Autumn Festival today. Let's have dinner together.
اليوم هو عيد منتصف الخريف. فلنتناول العشاء معاً.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Today is the Mid-Autumn Festival.
اليوم هو عيد منتصف الخريف.
My family is all in Canada.
جميع أفراد عائلتي يعيشون في كندا.
I'm celebrating alone.
أحتفل وحدي.
I'm sorry,
أنا آسف،
I can't be with you.
لا أستطيع أن أكون معك.
I have something to do during the day.
لديّ بعض الأمور التي يجب عليّ القيام بها خلال النهار.
Is the coffee shop open today?
هل المقهى مفتوح اليوم؟
It's opened till 4 o'clock.
يفتح حتى الساعة الرابعة مساءً.
Are you home?
هل أنت في المنزل؟
I think I forgot to add vinegar.
أعتقد أنني نسيت إضافة الخل.
It's fine. Having food is good enough.
لا بأس. وجود الطعام يكفي.
It smells delicious. Try it quickly.
رائحته شهية. جربه بسرعة.
Really?
حقًا؟
Look at this roe.
انظر إلى هذا البيض.
Not bad at all.
ليس سيئاً على الإطلاق.
Right?
يمين؟
You came just in time.
لقد أتيت في الوقت المناسب تماماً.
Want some crab?
هل ترغب ببعض السلطعون؟
No, thanks.
ًلا شكرا.
I brought you some mooncakes.
أحضرت لك بعض كعكات القمر.
Where did all these crabs come from?
من أين أتت كل هذه السرطانات؟
They were all gifts from clients to Boss.
كانت جميعها هدايا من العملاء إلى المدير.
But Boss has a cold and fever recently,
لكن الرئيس مصاب بنزلة برد وحمى مؤخراً،
so can't eat cold-natured food.
لذا لا يمكن تناول الأطعمة ذات الطبيعة الباردة.
That's why we get to enjoy them.
ولهذا السبب نستمتع بها.
Your boss is sick?
هل مديرك مريض؟
Seems he caught a cold over the weekend
يبدو أنه أصيب بنزلة برد خلال عطلة نهاية الأسبوع
and got sick.
ثم مرض.
Out to greet guests?
هل أنت ذاهب لاستقبال الضيوف؟
Are you going to pay me?
هل ستدفع لي؟
I can't afford you.
لا أستطيع تحمل تكاليفك.
I haven't even named my price.
لم أحدد السعر بعد.
Boss.
رئيس.
Finished with your IV drip?
هل انتهيت من تركيب المحلول الوريدي؟
So quick today?
هل كان الأمر سريعًا جدًا اليوم؟
It's fine.
لا بأس.
Well...
حسنًا...
You should go home early for the holiday.
ينبغي عليك العودة إلى المنزل مبكراً لقضاء العطلة.
-Thank you, Boss.
شكراً لك يا رئيس.
He said he had something to do during the day.
قال إنه لديه شيء يفعله خلال النهار.
So that "something" was actually getting an IV drip.
إذن، كان ذلك "الشيء" عبارة عن تلقي محلول وريدي.
Going to the hospital alone on a festival.
الذهاب إلى المستشفى بمفردي في أحد المهرجانات.
I would have gone with him if I had known.
كنت سأذهب معه لو كنت أعرف.
Still having a fever?
هل ما زلت تعاني من الحمى؟
Feel for yourself.
جرب بنفسك.